7133 Glencoe Ln., Anacortes, WA 98221

Professional Summary:

A tech-savvy and people-focused technician with a sharp mind for problem solving and the communication skills to work with anyone. From teaching the basics all the way to providing a knowledgeable hand for executive support. Experienced at inventing and iterating processes, writing and refining documentation, managing team dynamics, and providing escalation support. Reliable, compassionate, always willing to learn, and a proven team asset.

Skills:

- Software administration for systems such as: Active Directory, Microsoft CRM, Outlook and OWA, Microsoft Office, Zuora, Mitel/Shoretel, etc.
- Hardware troubleshooting for laptops, desktops and peripherals
- Full Stack Web Developer (Python, Ruby on Rails, and MEAN)
- Programming experience in Batch and SQL
- Corporate communication
- De-escalation and conflict resolution
- Adaptability and swift learning
- Experienced point of escalation
- Documentation writing and maintenance

Work History:

IT Service Desk Technician II, August 2017 – April 2023

Trupanion Pet Insurance

- First in line as the escalation point with the toolset to triage and resolve complex/sensitive issues
- Provided in-person and remote support to facilitate both the Seattle office and international operations
- Built, streamlined, and maintained the IT hiring process for over 5 years
- Wrote and maintained internal and user-facing documentation, including user on-boarding, off-boarding, account creation and remote VDI troubleshooting
- Volunteered for on-call rotation to provide after-hours support for international business expansion
- Developed good reputation and rapport with employees across all departments
- Won Trupanion's 2020 Team of the Year award for moving the business to a remote VDI system and providing training and hardware for over 1000 employees.

Data Assistant, December 2016 - August 2017

Trupanion Pet Insurance

- Exceeded service levels with a high degree of accuracy and speed
- Worked with customers and hospital clinics over the phone

Prep Cook, July 2015 - May 2016

Chandler's Square Retirement Community

- Worked tirelessly in a hectic and fast paced environment
- Provided thoughtful assistance and a friendly face for residents
- Kept to a strict timeline to ensure the kitchen ran smoothly

Education:

Coding Dojo Seattle, Graduated 2016

Full stack web development education

Anacortes High School, Graduated 2015